-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=破烂熊字幕组=-翻译：黎巴嫩 LULU 校对&时间轴：偶爱李小鹏
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-片名:无忧无虑
通往现实的路
The Road To Reality.
我可不想去
Don't wanna be going there.
你好啊
Hiya.
这里是安静的绿洲 外面却充满疯狂
An oasis of calm in here, mad out there.
不过天气可是真好啊 不是吗
Gorgeous day for it, though, innit?
以前没来过这呢
Never been in here before.
我喜欢你的帽子
I like your hat.
忙吗
Busy?
喂
Hello?
今天过得不好吗
Having a bad day?
没有啊
No.
哦 直到我出现?
Oh. Not till I showed up, eh?
像个慌乱的小兔子
Look like a rabbit caught in the headlights.
我不咬人的
I won't bite.
别担心 我就走了
Don't worry, I'm going now.
一切顺利 要开心哦
Have a good day. Stay happy.
我没偷东西哦 真的哦
I ain't nicked nothing. Honest, guv'nor.
哔哔哔哔 (防盗报警器的声音)
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
哦 不 不要 拜托...
Oh, no, no, come on.
真是太聪明了 真是聪明
That's just brilliant, that is.
不要啊 我还没来得及说再见呢
no, I didn't even get a chance to say goodbye.
* 你永远都回不去了 当夜里难以入睡 *
u'll never get it right cos when u're laid in bed at night
* 注视...蟑螂在墙上散步 *
Watching... roaches climb the wall
* 如果叫老爸 他会帮你赶走他 *
If you called your dad he could stop it all
* 你永远都无法像正常人一样生活 *
You'll never live like common people
* 你永远无法做普通人做的事 *
You'll never do what common people do
* 你永远无法像我们一样感受到失败 *
You'll never fail like common people
* 你永远都看不到你的生命从眼前消逝 *
You'll never watch your life slide out of view
* 跳舞吧 喝酒吧 疯狂吧 *
And dance and drink and screw
* 因为你没别的选择 *
Because there's nothing else to do
音乐停了
The music's stopped.
几年前就停了
It stopped ages ago.
是啊 我正享受安静呢
Yeah, I was just enjoying the silence.
什么事
What?
什么事这么开心
What's so funny?
我不知道
I don't know!
你们能不能...
Can you just...
哦 你妹妹醒了 波比
Oh, your sister's woken up, Poppy.
苏西 怎么了啊
Suzy, what's that?
怎么回事 你最近征服的那个吗
What is it? Is that your latest conquest?
哦 上帝保佑他
Oh, bless him!
你有没有曾经祈祷过你是被收养的 苏西
Don't you ever pray that you're adopted, Suzy?
有啊
Yeah.
你射中我了 祖
You got me, Zoe.
嘘      你让谁嘘呀
Ssssh!      Who are you shushing?
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
她说的对 我们一起享受这份安静吧
She's right. Let's all enjoy the silence together.
唐恩 你能闭上嘴吗 别人都插不上嘴了
Dawn,will u shut up?'cause no-one else can get a word in
嘘!
Ssssssh!
不好意思
Sorry!
嘘      手指放嘴唇上
Sssssh        Fingers on lips.
手指在咪咪上
Fingers on the tits.
手指放咪咪上      手指放屁屁上
Fingers on tits.        Fingers on the hips.
我可以借你的咪咪吗
Can I borrow yours?
手指放咪咪上      真恶心
Fingers on the tits.        that is properly disgusting.
鸡胸肉 谁要吃中饭
Chicken fillets. Lunch, anyone?
哦 喂?      给我试试行吗
Oh, hello!        Can I have a go?
当然可以 唐恩 这还用问么
Of course you can, Dawn, you don't need to ask.
那边有人要试试吗      哦 我知道是从哪来的
Anyone over there?        Oh, I know where that's been.
我对你的好感急转直下了
You have gone down in my estimation.
对不起 艾丽丝
I'm sorry, Alice.
我不明白你为什么要戴这个 波比      是吗?
I don't get why u wear them, Poppy.        don't u?
我是说 你把他们放在内衣里
I mean, you just put them in your bra...
怎么了
Yeah?
我喜欢他们给我的感觉 苏西
I like the way they make me feel, Suzy.
像个女人      没错
Like a natural woman.        That's right.
我觉得放错地方了
I think it's in the wrong place.
瞧 你有三个咪咪
look, you've got three tits!
她跟你一模一样 祖
She's like you, Zoe.
不 那是三个乳头      哦 对哦
No, that's three nipples.        Oh, right.
你有三个乳头吗
Have you got three nipples?
她不喜欢提起这个 我来抱抱她
She doesnt like to talk about it.I'm gonna give her a little hug
我来了     感觉真好 再来一次吧
Over u go.        Oh, that's quite nice. Do that again.
真的? 哦!
Oh, really? Oh!
你的乳沟在这个角度看起来真漂亮
Your cleavage looks great from up here.
谢谢      我在鸟瞰哦
Thank you.        I've got a bird's eye view.
拜托 姐妹们 快来看看这个
Come on, ladies, cop a load of this.
哦 好吧 都过来 都过来
Oh, yeah, roll up, roll up.
看啊
Look at that!
很漂亮 是吧      真棒
It's good, isn't it?        They're amazing.
哦 不要 哦 不
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
我想我们知道今天晚上波比要睡哪了
I think we know where Poppy's sleeping tonight.
早上好
Morning.
该起床了 懒虫
Time to get up, sleepyhead.
来杯茶吧
Cup of tea here.
快点 快起来
Come on. You can do it.
就这样 就这样 马上起来了
That's it. That's it, nearly there.
哦 再加把劲
Oh, here we go.
她起来了 很好      谢谢
And she's up! Hey.        Thanks.
你还好吧
You all right?
恩 睡得不错
Yeah, I slept good.
我听出来了
I heard you.
你总是这样说
You always start that.
我不打呼噜      我知道 你从来不打
I don't snore.        I know. You never have.
我没有      我没有
I don't.        I don't.
他们还在睡么      没有 好几年前就走了
Are they still asleep?        No,they buggered off ages ago
是么      是啊
Did they?        Yeah.
哦 好吧
Oh, right.
几点了      差不多12点10分
What's the time?        About 10 past 12.
他们有点事要办      是吗
They've got a bit of work to do.        Have they?
唐恩要赶论文      真惨 你们什么时候考试
Dawn's late with her dissertation no.When're ur exams?
明天开始 三周      你没问题的
Three weeks tomorrow.        You'll be all right.
恩 我都完全麻木了
Yeah. I'm totally chilled out about it.
当然
Of course you are.
我很好      恩
I'm cool.        Yeah.
就是有点紧张
I'm just really stressed.
什么? 好像一个头疼的爱斯基摩人?
What? Like an Eskimo with a headache?
有人要吐司吗     有
Does anyone want any toast?        Yeah.
我也要      要果酱的 两片
Yes, please.        With marmalade, two slices.
恩 知道了 要沿对角线切
Yeah, I know, cut on the diagonal.
恩      不要面包皮
Yeah.        No crusts.
知道了 哦 你们知道么      什么
Got it. Oh, do you know what?         What?
哦 天      她死了
Oh, yeah.        She's gone.
问题是 我们要从刑事司法开始考
The thing is, we're starting with criminal justice.
第一门考这个?      是啊 糟透了
Is that your first exam?        Yeah, it's crap.
如果先考信息犯罪 或者 犯罪与愉悦
If we had cyber crime first or like crime and pleasure
我会比较容易进入状态
I could ease myself into it.
没问题的      恩 你会没事的 苏西
No probs.        Oh, you'll be all right, Suzy.
是啊 如果我们都能拿到学位 那傻子都能
Yeah, if we can get a degree, any idiot can.
你管你妹妹叫傻子?      叫你傻子呢
You calling your sister an idiot?        Calling you an idiot.
谢谢
Thank you.
"犯罪与愉悦" 听起来不错
"Crime and pleasure", now that sounds good.
听起来像昨天晚上      是啊
Sounds like last night.        Yeah.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
恩
Yeah.
晚点见      再见
See you later.        Alligator
我们什么时候去看海伦      她宝宝什么时候出世
When're we going to see Helen?       when's the baby due?
不知道 快了吧 她一直在给我发信息
Don't know, soon. She's been texting me.
我也收到了 她情况越来越不好      我知道 保佑她
Me too, she's getting worse.        I know, bless her.
想等你考完试再说      我也想赶紧过去
Want to wait till after ur exams?        I want to get it over with.
好的 放心吧 把她交给我吧
All right. Don't worry, leave her to me.
发信息给我啊      加油
Text me, yeah?        Work hard.
苏西 你知道应该是往那边走的吧?
Suze... you know it's that way, don't you?
哦 是哦
Oh, yeah.
这样可以让腿变漂亮      很好
These make good legs?        Great.
能飞该多好啊 是吧      是吗
It would be amazing to fly,wouldn't it?        u reckon?
就这样... 嗖!
Just... whoosh!
嗯? 就想昏头先生那样?      哦 是啊 我爱死那本书了
What? Like Mr Vertigo?        Oh, yeah. I love that book.
恩      哦, 秃鹫
Yeah.        Oh, vultures.
见过几只      这些可能有用
Met a few of them.        These could be useful.
是啊 真棒 看看 他真漂亮
yeah, they're great. look at him, he's gorgeous.
我们可以扮猫头鹰 他们脑袋很大
We could do an owl, they've got big heads.
好主意 他眼睛真像你 看
Good idea. He's got your eyes, look.
谢谢啊 波比      没有啦 他们很可爱
Cheers, Poppy.        No, they're lovely.
鸽子迁徙么
Do penguins emigrate?
什么? 他们会搬到阳光海岸么
What? Do they move to the Costa del Sol?
迁徙 移居 随便啦
Emigrate, migrate, whatever.
鹦鹉怎么样?      哦 肯定行
What about parrots?        Oh, yeah, definitely.
或者巨嘴鸟 看她的嘴      颜色真鲜艳
Or a toucan.look at his beak.        They're good colours
很漂亮
Beautiful.
对了 你要去买个新自行车么
So, are u going to get another bike?
不买 不能替代我的旧爱 它已经展翅高飞了
no,I couldn't replace my old lovely.It's flown the nest now
不管怎么样 一定要去学开车了
Definitely going to learn to drive, though.
准备去报名了?      可能会吧
Going to book lessons?        Might do.
也可能不会
Might not.
我告诉你 不要用我的车学开车
I told you, you're not learning to drive in my car.
疯子
Nutter.
小鸡 我们扮小鸡      小鸡又不会飞
Chickens we could do chickens        Chickens don't fly
懒鬼 那我们扮什么呢?
Lazy buggers.What are we going to make, then?
我不知道啊 你认为呢      我也不知道
I don't know. What do you think?        I don't know.
眼睛在哪了?      这儿
Where are they?        Here.
这么远 是吧      是啊 别戳到我
That far apart, are they?        Yeah. Don't poke me.
根本碰不到你的
Wasn't going near you.
行了      很好
Go on, then.        Great.
你应该找个成年人来帮你
You should ask an adult to help you.
我不认识成年人
I don't know any.
我觉得非常好      是啊 你觉得怎样
I think they're quite good.        Yeah,what do u reckon?
我想我们可以套上这个      可以
I think we could pull in these.        Definitely.
去酒吧吗?      好啊 以毒攻毒
Pub?        Yeah, hair of the dog.
我好了 涂点唇膏马上就走
I'm ready. Put a bit of lippy on and away we go.
嗨 利兹      嗨 祖 你好
Hi, Liz.        Hi, Zoe. How are you?
不好意思
Didn't expect that one!
早啊 缇娜
Morning, Tina.
住在北美的鸟
Birds that live here in North America,
他们一路飞到南美
they fly all the way to South America.
恩?
Yeah?
这可是非同一般的旅行哦
That's a journey and a half, isn't it?
但是 鸟类中旅行最久的是北极燕鸥
But the biggest journey of them all is of the arctic tern.
因为他从北极...
Because he flies from the Arctic...
看到了吗  一路...穿过整个世界 到达南极
Yeah?all the way across the world to the South Pole
是不是很不可思议啊
Isn't that incredible?
从北极到南极一共有... 嘘!
From the North to the South Pole and that is... ssh!
一共有9300公里 没错
And that is 9,300 miles. That's right.
很好 尼克 现在把另一面也画上
All right, Nick, do the other side now.
就好了 看 不 不要拿出来
Here we go, look. No, don't pull it out.
我们要做的...
What we can do
我们给他... 我们给他画些点吧
Shall we give him Shall we give him a few bits?
你是想给他... 我喜欢 我喜欢
Do you want to give him...I like that, I like that.
我们可以给他在这画一个吗      不行
Shall we give him one here?        No.
不行?
No?
他有眉毛呢 看
He's got eyebrows, look.
是么      我看看
Yeah?        Let me see.
我觉得很好 非常好
I think that's brilliant. That's brilliant.
来
Here we go.
我可以在这里加点黄色吗 好了
Shall I put some more yellow in that? There we go.
你觉得你的羽毛应该是什么颜色
What colours do you think ur feathers could be?
看到了没 你可以画出彩虹的颜色
See u could do a rainbow colour.
真是个好主意 对吧
That's a good idea, isn't it?
我画了个彩虹
I did a rainbow.
画个彩虹 彩虹的颜色 就像鹦鹉那样
Do a rainbow. Rainbows like parrots.
先不要戴上
Don't put that on yet.
我们先看看
Let's have a look.
再多点 边缘这边怎么样
Little bit more. What about the fringing?
你可以在边上再多些颜色 你觉得呢
u could do a bit more on the fringing there,couldn't u?
饿了? 马上就到午饭时间了
Hungry? It's going to be lunch time soon.
虽然我不是厨师 但午饭马上就要开始了
But I'm not a cook. It's lunch time in a minute.
马上我们就吃午饭
We're going to lunch in a minute.
你们可以先去洗手
You can wash your hands.
谁准备好了?
Who's ready?
嘿!
Hey!
真棒! 你们真棒!
That is fantastic. Look at you go!
挥动你们的胳膊 拍打翅膀
Flap your arms. Flap your wings.
有点危险 是吗
Bit dangerous, innit?
怎么了
What?
把那些东西套在他们头上
Putting these over their heads.
我想憋死他们 那是我的目标 一群小坏蛋
I'm trying to suffocate them.That's my goal Little buggers
他们看上去棒极了      你周末过得怎样?
They look great.        How was your weekend?
糟透了     怎么回事?
Crap.        no, why's that, then?
没干什么 就在家呆着了 真的
I didn't do much, just stayed in, really.
周末啊 塔诗
It's the weekend, Tash.
我知道 我跟我妈发生了点口角      是吗
I know. I had a run-in with my mum.        Did ya?
我姐姐周六要上班 我就得去看着杰斯明
My sister's working Saturday.I had to look after Jasmine
她怎么了      这小姑娘吃太多了
How is she?        That girl eats too much.
上帝保佑
Bless her.
她吃了三个鸡腿 四个汉堡
She ate three chicken legs and four jam tarts
然后告诉我 她要饿死了
and then wants to tell me she's starving.
真是个小猪
The little piglet.
我把她丢到我妈妈那去了      是吗
I dropped her off to my mum's.        Yeah?
我说 你得告诉雪伦妮
I said u've got to tell Sherryanne
她得让这个小姑娘节食
she needs to put this girl on a diet
你反应过激了吧 她才7岁
You'll give her a complex, she's 7.
我妈突然不想管这事儿了
All of a sudden Mum doesn't want to get involved
她这辈子头一回
for the first time in her life.
然后我刚要走 我的两个姑姑就从多勒丝山来了
Then I'm just leaving the house my two aunts arrive from Dollis Hill.
不会吧
Oh, no.
然后我们就开始进行审判
So we get the Spanish Inquisition.
"塔诗 你有男朋友吗?"
"Tash, you got a boyfriend?
"是不是要结婚了呀?
"Are you getting married soon?
怎么不再给你妈妈添个孙子啊?"
Why don't u give your mother another grandchild?
你也知道她都快60岁了 都老了"
You know she nearly 60. She getting old."
我就说 "我没有男朋友
I was, like, "I haven't got a boyfriend.
也没有马上要结婚
I won't be getting married soon,
不 我也不会在近期内投资基金
no, I won't be investing in a mortgage in the near future
非常感谢你们的关心."
thank you very much."
然后我关上门就走了      结束
Then I just closed the door and left.        End of.
你在做饭      是啊 你也做饭?
You cooking?        Yeah, are you cooking?
我要用天然气做饭 我们吃什么
I'm cooking with gas. What we having?
吃的      还真特别
Food.        That makes a change.
你饿吗      饿得发疯了
Are you hungry?        I'm ravishing.
谁说不是呢      谢谢
Aren't you just.        Thank you.
今天进行的怎样?
How did it go today?
什么? 跟我哪些长满羽毛的的飞行团?
What, with my flying flock of feathered friends?
很好 他们很喜欢 飞得很开心
Good, they loved it. Flapping away they were.
是吗      是啊 上帝保佑
Were they?        Yeah, bless them.
我不得不在他们飞出窗子之前
I had to nip it in the bud with my lot
先把他们都扼杀了
before they flew out the window.
不管怎样 还不错 对吧
It was OK, though, was it?
是啊 吃完午饭以后我给他们放音乐
Oh, yeah, I played them Stravinsky
来让他们安静下来
after lunch just to calm them down.
你放哪首曲子      春之祭
What did you play?        The Rite Of Spring.
我定好了我的第一堂驾驶课
I booked my first driving lesson.
是吗      是啊
Did you?        Yeah.
什么时候?      周六 12点
When is it?        12 o'clock, Saturday.
好极了 干得好
Excellent, well done you.
我去收拾桌子      好 快好了
I'll set the table.        Yeah, it's nearly ready.
恩 我知道
Yeah, I know.
我喜欢周末      你没说过
I love the end of the week.         You don't say.
真的 我喜欢      是吗
I do, actually.        Do you?
是啊      哦
Yeah.        Oh.
你知道么 我周五下午上舞蹈课
u know I take this dance class on a Friday afternoon
那可是黄金时间
the golden time.
我发誓 一半的孩子都比我大
I swear to God, half the kids are bigger than me.
那也不太难 是吧?
That's not hard, though, is it,  titch?
不 我不是说比我高 而是比我知道的多
No, I don't mean taller, I mean wider.
你得小心点 知道吧?
You want to be careful, you know?
你不会想让孩子们跳起来介绍他们自己的
u don't want kids jumping about expressing themselves
有点危险
A bit dangerous.
是 你都是在周五跳舞
Yeah, you do all that on Friday,
然后他们就在家过周末 不出门
but then they spend the weekend indoors,
黏在游戏机上
glued to their Nintendo DS.
真是这么回事 两周前 我周一到教室
Totally. A couple of weeks ago I came in Monday
我跟波比说 让孩子坐下开始交流时间
I told Poppy sat the kids down for carpet time,
问问他们周末都干什么了
asked them what they did over the weekend.
多好的天气啊 竟然没有一个人出去过
Gorgeous weather. Not one of them had been out.
他们全都呆在家里打游戏
They'd all been sitting at home on their PlayStations.
他们坐地毯上 你怎么都弄不起来
You couldn't get them up off the carpet.
等他们起来了 一个个都气喘吁吁
When they got up, they were wheezing.
真是污染你啊      我们以前都去公园的
That's pollution for u        We always used to go to park
很多孩子都没有公园可去      恩 很对
A lot of them don't have parks to go to.        Ye, exactly
但是散步的话也不需要去公园啊
But you don't need a park to go for a walk.
如果爸爸妈妈都不出去 孩子也不会
If Mum and Dad don't go out, the kids don't.
家长们都不敢让孩子们出去玩
Parents are too frightened to let their kids play out.
就算是附近有绿地 也不让他们在那玩
Even a bit of green by estate they don't let them play there.
但对很多父母来说 的确是够艰难的 不是吗
But it's hard for a lot of mums and dads, isn't it?
在强大工作压力下拼命做一个星期
They've had a hell of a week.under pressure and stress.
说的是啊      下班回来还要在家里工作
Tell me about it.    They get back from work if they work...
你知道的 当中很多都是单亲妈妈 她们累坏了
u know.A lot of them're single mums they're exhausted.
如果她们没有带孩子们去野餐也是可以理解的
It's understandable if they don't take their kids out for a lovely picnic.
我不能接受
It's not acceptable.
生活是艰辛
Life's hard,
但如果真的想办法 还是会想到的 不是么
but if u want to find a way you find it, innit?
有些父母不想被烦      是啊 我知道
Some parents can't be bothered.         Yeah, I know.
所以他们宁愿让孩子在聊天室待到大半夜
So they let their kids stay up half night on chat rooms
是啊      是啊 真让人担心
Yeah!        Yeah, that's worrying.
恐怖      真让人生气
Scary.        Makes me so angry.
很多7岁的孩子 对于网络知道的比我们还多
A lot 7-year-olds know more about internet than we do
至少人们已经在关注这个事情了 还是不错的
At least people are talking about it. That's good.
是吗      是啊 这说明我们已经意识到了
Is it?        yeah. It means we're aware.
我知道吸烟对我不好 但不代表我要戒了
I'm aware smoking's bad for me It doesn't mean I'll stop
只要你知道什么能害死你就行      谢谢
As long as you know what will kill you.        Thanks
不客气
Any time.
我知道喝酒对我不好 但你知道
I know drinking's bad for me, but, you know...
我控制不住
I can't help myself.
哦 丢人      干杯!
Oh, shame.        Cheers!
干杯 朋友们
Cheers, everyone!
为我们的肝 以及溺死在里面的一切
Here's to our livers and all who drown in them.
小心点 波比 明天是你第一节驾驶课
Careful, Poppy u got ur first driving lesson tomorrow.
哦 对哦 快点 快放下来
Oh, yeah, quick, put that down.
别把你的盲区搞砸了
You don't want to mess up your blind spot.
听起来不错      看这 有几根手指?
that sounds good.        it's here.How many fingers?
肯定是找你的      我太兴奋了
That must be for you.        I'm so excited!
你应该在进车之前做几个深呼吸
u should do some deep breathing before u get in the car.
看不到他 祝我好运吧
can't see him. Wish me luck.
好运 我会叫紧急救护人员准备好的
Good luck I'll keep the emergency services on standby
还有什么借口?      我知道你喜欢消防员
Any excuse, eh?        I know what u're like with firemen
你好 是斯科特吗
Hello. Scott?
你是波比?      是我 很高兴见到你
Are u Poppy?        That's me. Nice to you meet u.
是的 车在这儿
Right, the car's just here.
没有传染病的 你怎么了?
They're not infected! What are you like?
手是干净的 其实我刚刚还特意洗了洗
They're clean, I just washed them specially,honest.
这就是练习车?      你坐乘客的位置
This it?        You get in the passenger seat.
你知道是我要学开车吗
You know it's me learning to drive?
知道 但有几件事情得先讲清楚
Yeah But we have to talk a few things through.
是吗 有道理 如果你坚持的话
have we? Fair enough. If you insist.
你选的这辆彩色的车?      不要拘束
Did u choose this colour car? Make urself comfortable.
谢谢 这是你的车吗?      不 是公司的车
Thank u Is this ur car?        No, it's the company's car
对哦 那你的车是什么样子的?      这就是我的车
right,what's ur car like, then?        It is my car
你说这是公司的车呀 你可想准了啊
u said it was the company's car Make your mind up.
你有临时驾照那?      有的
Have u got your provisional licence?        Yep!
给你 我那天状态不怎么好
There you go. That's me on a bad day.
这是你的真名吗 波琳?      对
Is that your real name, Pauline?        Right.
好 看起来一切正常      是吗 那太好了
OK,everything seems to be in order.        Does it? That's good.
你以前上过驾驶课吗
have u ever had a driving lesson before?
上过 也不算是真正的驾驶课
Yeah.No,it wasn't really a lesson.
在迈阿密开一辆凯迪拉克
It was in a Cadillac in Miami.
在沙滩上横冲直撞
Bunny-hopped down the beach.
我喝醉了 很好玩
I was a bit pissed, it was hilarious.
我们开这辆车时 不能喝酒 明白吗
We won't be pissed when driving this car, OK?
也不会横冲直撞 我们要集中 专注
We're not going to bunny-hop We'll focus concentrate.
我带你去场地 学员都在那学
I'm going to take u to a spot we take all learner drivers.
真的吗      我们要通过驾驶室训练
Are you?        We'll go through the cockpit drill
可真调皮      好好听讲 负责一点
naughty.        You'll listen and take responsibility.
我会努力的
I'll see what I can do.
好 系好安全带      马上 斯科特船长
OK.Put ur seat belt on.        Will do, Captain Scott.
出发啦 小男人
Here we go, gigolo.
你给办公室打过电话吗     是啊 跟你老板通过电话
So u spoke to the office?        Yeah I spoke to ur boss.
他不是我老板 我给自己打工
He's not my boss, I work for myself. I'm my own man.
但这是他的车...或者 你的车... 还是某人的
But it's his car... or it's your car... Someone.
他们告诉你价钱了吗 一个小时两块五
And they told you the price ?2.50 an hour?
是啊 跟薯条一样便宜 你真行
That's right. Cheap as chips, you lot.
我们价钱低 但是我们更出色      是吗
We may be cheap but we're better.        Are you?
你选大公司 可他们用的是没经验的教官
u go with big companies,they use inexperienced instructors
没经验?
They don't?
他们只是通过了一些考试 就多收钱
They've just passed their test and charge more.
混蛋
Bastards.
我们这些有经验的教官 我们去小公司 收钱少
Us experienced instructors,go with small companies charge less
这样更合理      价钱低是相对的
That makes a lot of sense that does.     Cheapness is relative
的确 你说的对 一语中的!
Yeah, it is. You're right. Bang-on!
那么 下周还是同一时间吗
So, do you want the same time every week?
到时候继续
Go on, then.
是或不是? 我得知道      如果你需要知道的话
Do u or don't u? I need to know.        if u need to know.
你没问题 那我就没问题 斯科特
If it's good for you, it's good for me, Scott.
好吧 就每周六12点
OK, 12 o'clock every Saturday.
你喜欢周六上班吗      我周六就工作半天
Do u like working Saturdays?        I only work half day,Saturday.
真好      你是我最后一个学生
that's good.        You're my last pupil.
那你剩下的时间干吗呢
What do u do for rest of day?
你今晚出去玩吗
Are u going out tonight?
我会回家 看书
I shall go home and read my book.
肯定是本好书 什么名字
it must be a good book. What is it?
就是一本书
It's a book.
这样啊 好吧 至少我们知道了一些事情
Yeah, well, we worked that much out.
你看到你前面这三个踏板了吧      恩 看到了
u see three pedals in front of you.        Yeah, yeah.
把左脚踩在左边的踏板上 然后一路踩下去
Will u put left foot on left-hand pedal push it all the way down?
他还挺活泼的 是吧
He's a bit frisky, isn't he?
好的 波琳 把脚从踏板上拿开吧
OK, Pauline. Please take ur boot off the pedal.
从我两岁开始就没人叫我波琳了
Nobody's called me Pauline since I was 2 years old.
让我觉得好笑
Makes me laugh.
那我应该叫你什么
What am I supposed to call you?
哦 波比怎么样      波比?
Oh, how about Poppy?        Poppy?
对      哦 好吧
Yeah.        Oh, yeah.
不 随便叫什么 斯科特 我不介意的
No,whatever turns u on, Scott. I don't mind.
好的 波比 你的靴子不太适合上驾驶课
OK,Poppy.ur boots're inappropriate for a driving lesson
我的鞋怎么了      穿高跟鞋控制不好车
What's wrong with them?u can't control a car in high heels.
我穿高跟鞋可以做很多事
I can do a lot in these.
你应该看看我学跳舞的时候
u should see me in these on a dance floor.
高跟鞋可能很适合舞蹈课
They may be good on a dance floor
不止适合舞蹈课
Not just good on a dance floor.
他们很棒!
They are "Oooh".
可能适合你坐在沙滩上的凯迪拉克里
They may be good in a Cadillac on a beach
当你跟男朋友喝得酩酊大醉的时候
when you're pissed with your boyfriend,
但驾驶课就不适合
but they're not suitable for driving.
你很风趣
You're funny.
我希望你下周能穿平底鞋来
Now, next week I want u to bring flat-soled shoes.
我穿平底鞋不怎么好看      不管你好不好看
I don't look any good in them.        It's not how u look,
你是要学怎么开车
it's how you drive.
我看能不能为你搞到一双了 斯科特 我来解决
I'll see what I can rustle up for u,Scott.Leave it to me.
好了 你看到三面镜子
Right, you see three mirrors
两面侧视静 一面后视镜
ur two side-view mirrors and your rear-view mirror.
他们组成了一个黄金三角形
They make a golden triangle.
就像阴部三角区一样吗?
Is that like the pubic triangle?
就像是一个金字塔 在顶端
It's a pyramid and at the top of it
有只可以洞穿一切的眼睛 "因哈拉"
u see the all-seeing eye Enrahah.
你可以重复一下吗 "因-拉-哈"
Can you repeat that, please? "En-ra-hah".
你是说路西法之眼吗      不是
You talking about the eye of Lucifer?        No!
因为我不知道能否把注意力集中到那 谢谢
Cos I don't know if I want to look in there, thank you.
不是路西法 在路西法之前还有两个堕落天使
It's not Lucifer.There are two fallen angels before Lucifer.
有因拉哈 拉结尔 然后才是 路西法
There is Enrahah Raziel and Lucifer.
我没他们的电话号码
I don't have them in my phone book.
耐心听我说      他在哪
Bear with me.        Where is he?
听我说      我看不到他
Bear with me.        I can't see him.
只是个教学工具而已      是吗
It's a teaching tool.        Is it?
我先给你解释下一些关于教学的事情
Let me explain something to you about teaching.
老师的工作就是帮助学生养成好习惯
teacher's job is to bring out good habits in the pupil
改掉坏习惯
and to get rid of bad habits.
都是通过向学生重复这些思想做到的
He does that through frequent repetitive thinking.
他用清晰明了的画面来反应这些思想
he does that by creating clear and distinct images
学生就很容易接受并且记住不忘
that are easy for the pupil to retain.
哦 现在也是吗      是啊
Oh, does he, now?        Yes.
别担心 已经烙在这里了
Don't worry, it's burnt in there.
你记住 你一直到死都会记得因拉哈
u remember.u will remember Enrahah till the day u die
那我就功德圆满了
and I will have done my job.
你为什么不说些好东西 比如大草莓什么的
Why don't u have sth nice up there like a giant strawberry?
你相信我 很管用
Believe you me, it works.
好了 住手      我现在干吗
OK, stop!        What am I doing now?
请把你的手从排挡上拿开 从变速杆上拿开
Please take ur hand off the gear. Off the gear stick!
好吧      脚从踏板上拿开
All right.        Foot off the pedal.
我什么都不动了      我给你解释些事情
I'm not touching anything.        Let me explain to you sth
我就靠这辆车活了 这车是我的全部
This car is my livelihood.This car is how I earn my living.
我不知道你是干什么的      恩
I don't know how you earn your living.        Yeah.
但如果我走进你的酒吧 你的舞池 或者俱乐部
But if I walked into ur pub or ur discotheque or ur club
然后走向DJ 刮花他所有的碟片
and I walked up to the DJ I scratched all his records,
或者 我砸碎所有的杯子
or I smashed all the glasses,
然后我说 "对不起 我不知道我做了什么"
I said,"I'm sorry,I didn't know what I was doing"
你肯定不能接受
that wouldn't be acceptable.
那我有个问题
There is only one problem with that.
我没有酒吧 也没有舞厅
I don't own a bar or a disco.
我就是个小学老师
I'm just a primary school teacher.
你是小学老师?      恐怕是的 孩子
Are you?        Afraid so, kiddo.
你是撒旦崇拜者吗 斯科特
Are you a Satanist, Scott?
不是 刚好相反
No,in fact I'm exactly the opposite.
那你信教皇喽
Are you the Pope, then?
那是一回事      是吗 他知道吗
That's the same thing.        Is it? Does he know that?
好了 你有三个踏板 A B C
Right, you have three pedals, A, B, C.
油门 刹车 离合器
Accelerator, brake and clutch.
继续讲 亲爱的
Talking about... Lovely.
很好      恩
Good.        Yeah.
他长什么样
What's he like?
你会喜欢他的      会吗
You'd love him.        Would I?
他让我发笑 他很好玩
He made me laugh. He was funny.
什么样的 是哈哈大笑 还是怪怪的笑
What? Like funny "Ha ha" or funny peculiar?
实际上都有点吧      然后呢
Bit of both, actually.        So, what happened, then?
他冲着我大喊      什么 他训你了?
He shouted at me.        What? He gave u a telling off?
他那人有点拘谨 有那么点
He's a little bit uptight. Just a little bit.
肯定是你激他了      把你介绍给他吧
Bet you wound him up.        Might set you up with him.
他看上去健康吗      是的
Is he fit?        Yeah.
不 他看上去一点也不健康 不过就是适合你
No, he's not fit at all. Just your type.
有我什么好处啊      你就可以随时打炮了
What do I get out of it?        u get a shag whenever u want.
上次是什么时候
When was the last time that happened?
是谁的错 恩? 你要去哪 苏西
Who's fault's that, eh? Where are u going? Suzy!
你还好吧       好?
You all right?        All right?
发生什么事了      走吧
What's going on?        Come
你冲着我妹妹大喊大叫      我没有
u shouting at my little sister?        No.
看上去不像啊 是吧      波比
Doesn't look like it, does it?        Poppy!
你要去哪      你给我滚
Where are you going?        Fuck off!
别跟着我们 聪明点 再见
Not coming with us, apparently. Adios.
苏西
Suze!
早上好 波比      还好吧?
Morning, Poppy.        All right?
你怎么了      后背劳损了
What's the matter?        Buggered my back,haven't I?
看上去好像是      玩蹦床玩的
Looks like it.         Trampolining.
蹦床? 真的假的?      恩 我每周都去
Trampolining? Really?        Yeah, I go every week.
哦? 放学以后?      我很喜欢
What? After school?        I love it.
真不错
Great.
你得常常锻炼肌肉 做做拉伸运动
You've got to keep the muscles a-pumping.
因为我刚开始学佛拉明戈      是吗
Cos I've just started flamenco.        You haven't?
这舞超棒      我一直很想跳 像这样
It's fantastic.        I've always wanted to do it Bit of that.
小心点      我没事
Careful.        I'm all right.
一起来吧 如果你想来的话      什么时候
Come along, if you want.        When is it?
每周二 6点半
Every Tuesday, 6:30.
来吧 看看你感觉如何      好的
Well, see how you feel.        All right.
早上好 丽安      早
Morning, Leanne.        Morning.
这附近都是尿骚味儿
Stink of urine round here.
我什么都没闻到      你又尿裤子了吗
I can't smell anything.        Have u peed ur pants again?
恩 不好意思
Yeah, sorry.
淘气的姑娘      是啊
You're a naughty girl.        Tell me about it.
你没事吧      恩
You all right?        Yeah.
忍一忍 快到了
Come on, we're nearly there.
你是不是没嗅觉啦
Have u lost your sense of smell?
恩 抽烟抽得都闻不到味道了
Yeah, smoking dulls your senses.
脑子也没了 我们到了      上去吧
And your brain. Here we go.        Go on, then.
填好了
Done that.
全都好了?      是啊 谢谢
All done?        Yeah, thanks.
好
OK.
保重啊
Take care.
好了 下一个是谁?      波比-克劳斯
OK who have we got next?        Poppy Cross.
谢谢
Thanks.
波比?       不 我是祖 很高兴见到你
Poppy?        No, I'm Zoe. Nice to meet you.
不 我是波比 不好意思 不知道她是谁
No,I'm Poppy,sorry about her Don't know who she is.
我叫艾斯拉      你好艾斯拉
My name's Ezra.        Hello, Ezra.
请跟我上楼好吗      好的
You want to just follow me upstairs?        Yeah.
你块头儿真大       祝你好运
You're big, aren't you?        Good luck!
慢慢来      你要对我做什么
Just take ur time.        What are u going to do to me?
我想笑
Makes me laugh.
好了 我现在要感觉下你背部的肌肉
OK, I'm just going to feel the muscles in ur back.
好的      你告诉我哪里痛
Right.        And u let me know where the pain is.
我会给你发消息的
I'll send you a text.
手指很有力
Strong fingers.
好痒
That tickles.
就是这了!      好的
Bang on the money.        OK.
这边?
And this side?
恩
Yeah.
好的 试试看侧边向下伸 就像要去捡东西一样
OK.Do u want to reach down to ur side as if u're picking something up?
捡鸡肉
Picking chickens.
对不起 我做不到 啊!
No, sorry. I can't do that. Ow! Oooh.
是后背吗
Is it your back?
什么?
Sorry?
可以影响一切 是吧
Cos it can affect everything, can't it?
比如你的情绪啊 任何东西
Like your mood and everything.
;不错     仰面躺好
Nice action.        Lie on ur back for me, please.
一定要来这么一下 迟早会有用的
Must get one of these. Come in very handy.
好 现在我要你翻过身来侧躺着 面向我
OK I'm just going to ask u to roll urself onto ur side facing me.
你要求还真不过分啊 是吧
u don't ask for much do you, eh?
我现在要再次感觉下你脊椎上的肌肉
I'm going to feel the muscles in ur spine again.
好了
OK.
好了 躺回去
All right, lie back.
好了
There we go.
你脊柱上有一个关节扭到了
There's a joint in your spine that's jammed up.
哦 不要啊
Oh, no.
我帮你松一下怎么样?      严重吗
Would you like me to release it?        Is it serious?
不是很糟      你要怎么做?疼么?
It's not too bad.        What u going to do? Will it hurt?
可能会疼几天
It may for a few days.
让暴风雨来得更猛烈些吧      你确定?
Go on, then. Go for your life.        Are you sure?
如果你动作快的话
If you're quick.
好的
OK.
我现在要把你翻过来
I'm going to roll you over
你会感觉到后背咔嚓疼一下
and you'll feel a short sharp click in your back.
好吗 吸气....
OK? Breathe in. And...
哦 等会儿
Oh. Wait a minute.
好 准备好了吗
OK. Are you ready?
恩
Yeah.
好的 吸气...
OK, breathe in...
好      呼气...
OK.        And release.
好了 放松
OK. Just relax for me.
没想到你会那样做
Didn't know you were going to do that.
放松 调整到正常呼吸就好
Just relax and breathe normally.
好了 坐起来好吗
OK, would you like to sit up for me?
好的
Yeah.
以后会常常这样吗 随便改时间?
Will this be a regular occurrence, chopping changing?
对不起 斯科特 发生了点事情
Sorry, Scott. Something came up.
我也有自己的生活的
I've got a life too, you know.
我得去赴个约会      难道这个不是吗
I had to make an appointment.        Isn't this an appointment?
我没办法的
I couldn't help it.
黄泉路上好意多
The road to hell is paved with good intentions.
听起来挺好玩的
Sounds like fun.
今天过得不好 是吧
Having a bad day, are you?
今天早上遇到个坏学生      不是吧 他做什么了
I had a bad pupil this morning.       no, what did he do?
他迟到 拒付学费
He was late, he refused to pay his money.
摔车门 还骂我
He slammed the door and swore at me.
你骂他了吧      我开走了 再也不会教他
u shout at him,did u?        I drove off I'm not teaching him again.
给他点颜色看看      他很粗鲁 自大
You show him.        He's rude, he's arrogant,
他过于自信 太没素质了
he's overconfident and he's too street.
你不喜欢那样的
You don't like that.
惯坏了
He's been overindulged and
不停地表达他自己
encouraged to express himself.
他敢 剁掉他的手!
Express himself! Chop his hands off!
你知道他们那么做代表什么吗
Do you know what it means when they do that?
继续说     他们有多无知
Go on.        How little do they know.
他们老妈有多无知
How little do their mothers know.
而且他们很臭
And they smell.
你还真挺不容易的 是吧
It's not easy being you, is it? Eh?
见到你真好 嘿
Fancy meeting you here, hey?
你可以不用笑的 我放过你了
You don't have to laugh, I'll let you off.
好的 慢点 慢慢来
OK, gently, gently, gently, gently.
稳稳的来      对不起
Steady progression.        Sorry.
脚从刹车上拿开
Take your foot off the brake.
不用把脚放在刹车上
There's no need to put your foot on the brake.
知道现在是什么在踩刹车吗      是什么
Do you know what's doing that? What is doing that?
你的靴子 你的靴子在踩刹车
Your boots. Your boots are doing that.
不是 我在慢慢开
No, I was taking my time.
我有点乱了      你的靴子 不适合开车
I panicked.        Your boots, they're inappropriate.
好了 开始
OK, on.
波比 加油 来点速度 好吗
Poppy, come on. Let's pick up some speed. OK?
别冲着我大喊大叫 斯科特
Don't shout at me, Scott.
好了 别慢慢悠悠了 快开吧
Well, don't dilly dally, let's just go. OK.
我在学呢      接下来左转 好吗
I'm just learning.        Next left-hand turn. OK?
你吓到我了      好的 镜子 信号 移动
u panic me.        So, mirror, signal, manoeuvre.
开过去      因拉哈 因拉哈
Gets me right there.        Enrahah, Enrahah.
双手放在方向盘上 因拉哈 因拉哈
Both hands on the wheel,Enrahah Enrahah.
我不喜欢这样 让我觉得毛骨悚然
I don't like that, gives me the creeps.
波比 指示灯 镜子 信号 移动
Poppy. Indicate. Mirror, signal, manoeuvre.
指示灯      信号 对的
Indicate.        Signal, OK.
我开得怎样      脚踩刹车 离合器
How am I doing?        Foot down on the brake Clutch.
发动机别停 很好 找到联动点 看镜子 慢慢走
u don't want to stall OK,find ur biting point peep creep.
一档 看镜子 慢慢走      一档
First gear. Peep and creep.        First gear.
看镜子 慢慢往前走      正在看镜子 正在慢慢开
Peep and creep.        Peeping and a-creeping.
这条路开到头儿...      他真不错
When u get to the end of the road...        he's nice.
这条路开到头儿 专心开车好吗
When we get to end of the road Can u please focus on driving?
因拉哈 因拉哈
Enrahah, Enrahah.
因拉哈 好了!      我... 有点奇怪
Enrahah. OK!         I... That's a bit weird.
脚放刹车和离合器上 发动机别停
Foot on the brake,clutch.You don't want to stall.
找到联动点 有没有在山上的感觉
Find your bite. Can u feel you're slightly on a hill?
没有      好吧 拉手刹
No.        OK, put the hand brake on.
找联动点 好了 门锁好 门锁好
Find ur biting point. OK lock ur door. Lock your door.
别犯傻了      波比 有两扇门
Don't be ridiculous.        Poppy, there's two of them.
你要去撒尿吗      关上门
Are you taking the piss?        Lock your door.
我们走 波比 我们开车      真不敢相信你说出那样的话
let's go Let's go Poppy let's go I don't believe u just said that
走吧 继续开 继续开
Let's go. On you go. On you go.
我们走那条路吧      波比!波比! 继续开
Let's go that way.        Poppy! Poppy, let's go!
我们在拐弯处 快点走      哎呀
We're on a bend Now let's go        Blimey
很好 继续走 保持在路的左边
Right on u go Keep to the left of the centre of the road
下周同一时间
Usual time next week?
12点 如果你愿意的话 可以数一下
12 o'clock? You can check it if you like.
回见
See you.
再见哟
Cheerio.
你好啊 狗狗
All right, doggie?
再来一个
Here's another one.
圆圈 红色
Circle, completely red.
什么呢 像西红柿吗
What? Like a tomato?
举例 白色水平线
For instance. White horizontal line.
给点提示 祖
Give us a clue, Zoe.
水平的 跟水平线平行
Horizontal, parallel to the horizon.
谢谢 马诗老师
Thank you, Miss Marsh.
不客气      好吧 不像悠悠球那样一上一下的
u're welcome.        So, it's not... up down like a yoyo.
不像      好吧
No.        Right.
是什么      垂直的
What is it?        Vertical.
不是啦 笨蛋 标志是什么     应该是"禁止入内"
No, u muppet, the sign.        That'd be "no entry".
禁止什么      禁止骑自行车的黑人小男孩
For what?        For black boys on bicycles.
别让我又想起来啊
Don't get me started on that again.
就这么突然冒出来了
It just popped out of his mouth.
你可以另找一个教官的      我知道 看看再说吧
u can always get another instructor I know.See how it goes?
再来一个      还是一个红圆圈
Ask me another.         This is also a red circle.
黑色的车 跟种族歧视没关系
Black car, this isn't a racist thing.
很高兴听到这个      黑车旁边是个红色的车
Glad to hear it.        Next to the black car is a red car.
那是我的神奇先生超了傻瓜的车
That's Mr Golly overtaking Noddy.
因拉哈!      你也因拉哈!
Enrahah.        Enrahah to you.
是什么      禁止超车
What is it?        No overtaking.
因拉哈!      因啦哈-哈-哈!
Enrahah.        Enrahah-ha-ha!
他听起来像个疯子      他根本就是个疯子
He sounds like a nutter.        He is a nutter.
你的后背怎么样了?      还好了 被他治好了
How's your back?        It's all right actually.He sorted it.
魔法手指 他很帅 不是吗
Magic fingers.He was sweet, wasn't he?
他很健康
He was fit.
八边形标志 里面写了个 "停"
Octagonal sign with "stop" written in it.
停!      那好吧
Stop!        All right, then.
谁先眨眼睛?
Who's going to blink first?
想来杯茶吗      好的
Do you want a cup of tea?        Yes, please.
不 你今晚吃烤面条 我们明天把鸡吃完
No,u have lasagne tonight.We can finish chicken tomorrow
听着 我们现在不能聊了 待会儿见
Look, I can't talk now. See you later.
你觉得我们能到吗      看路况了
Do u think we'll make it?        Depends on the traffic.
应该没事的 哦 我的后背
Should be all right. Ooh, that's my back!
嘿 请进 女士们 快点快点
Hey, come in, ladies, as quick as you can.
想放包的话 那还有几个地方
Do want to put your bags, and there's a couple of places.
对不起我们迟到了      不好意思
Sorry we're late.        Sorry.
没关系 这非常有西班牙风格
No problem,it's very Spanish to be late.
选好位置 我们开始了
Take ur places. Then we can start.
站这吧
Here.
我刚刚向不认识我的人们 介绍了自己
I was just introducing myself to peoples don't know me.
再见到你真好 更好的是你还带了朋友来
It's lovely to see u again and lovely you bring a friend.
欢迎来上我的课
Welcome in my class.
好的 我的名字叫罗塞塔-桑托斯
So, my name is Rositta Santos
我来自西班牙的西维尔
and I'm coming from Sevilla in Spain.
或者塞维利亚 你们这里的叫法
Or Seville, what you say here.
那里以斗牛闻名 当然还有我们的橘子
What is famous for our bullfighting our beautiful oranges
你们英国人把橘子做成恶心人的果酱
what ur English peoples turn into disgusting marmalade
你是不是要一直戴着那个太阳眼镜
Are u going to keep those sunglasses on, then?
塞维利亚也是佛拉明戈的发源地
And also is the birth home of flamenco.
不好意思
Sorry.
现在大家都准备好了... 我希望是这样
Then everybody is ready... I hope
好的 双脚平行 提臀
So, feet in parallel. Hip distance apart.
腰部上提 扩胸
Pulling up from the waist.Opening across the chest.
肩胛骨沿脊椎向下拉
Shoulder blades drawing down to the spine.
手臂放松
Arms relaxed.
头向右伸
And taking the head over to your right.
感受一下脖子里的力道
Feeling that lovely stretch at the neck.
然后向左伸
Then to the left.
不是很佛拉明戈 是吗
Not very flamenco, is it?
向右
To the right.
头部转回中间
Bringing the head back to the centre.
放松 很好
And relax. Lovely.
好的 现在我们开始扩展腹肌
So, guys. We're going to reverse the abs now.
右脚在前
Right foot in front.
举起手肘 好像有线提着一样
Lifting up from the elbows.Like they got strings attached
好像小匹诺曹
Like little Pinocchio.
上提 上提
Lifting, lifting.
肩膀保持向下 手臂举过头顶
Keeping the shoulders down. Arms above the head.
注意面部表情 像这样... 骄傲一点
Framing the face. Here I am... proud.
然后把手臂从前面放下来 向下压 向下压
Then bringing the arms down in front.Pressing pressing
保持住张力 保持这个力度
Keeping the tension, keeping the strength,
但要流畅
but fluid as well.
再从肘部开始提升 就好像老鹰要展开它的双翼
lifting up again from the elbows Like eagle spreading his wings.
优美 愤怒 凶狠
Beautiful, angry, ferocious.
同学们 当你们提起你们的鹰翼的时候
guys, when you're lifting up your eagle wings,
要记得 这个舞蹈来源于痛苦 来自于煎熬
remember this dance comes from the pain,from suffering
的吉普赛男子
of los gitanos...
嗯就是你们口中的"吉普赛人"
what you say, "the gypsies".
我知道这个单词从政治意义上讲是不对的
I know this word not politically correct,
但这些人 他们被社会排挤了
but these guys, they been squashed down by society
好几个世纪 然后他们说
for centuries, centuries, and they say,
"我们不要这样 我们有自己的荣耀
"We don't need this. We got pride.
我们有尊严
We got dignity.
我们有心 我们有佛拉明戈"
We got heart. We got flamenco."
他们说 "这里... 我的世界"
They say, "This... my space."
我的世界
My space.
我的世界 同学们 这样做 一 二
My space.Everybody... do this. One, two.
我的世界
My space.
再来      我的世界
And again.        My space!
快点! 快点!       我的世界
Vamos! Vamos!        My space!
再来一次      我的世界
And again.        My space!
快点 快点      我的世界
Vamos, vamos.        My space!
充满了意义      我的世界
With meaning.        My space!
但是 同学们
But, guys.
我的世界
My space!
再来一次       我的世界
One more time.        My space!
面带表情        我的世界
With expression.        My space!
我不相信      我的世界
I don't believe it.        My space!
好了 同学们 现在分成两排
OK, guys. I'll give you two counts in.
然后我们边跺脚边拍手走到中间 好吗
we're going to stamp and clap the compass, OK?
1 2
Uno, dos.
同学们 同学们 你们在干什么
Guys, guys, guys. What are you doing?
激情呢 那种复仇的情绪呢 血性呢
Where is passion? Where is revenge? Where is blood?
这是佛拉明戈舞
This is flamenco.
你们拍手拍的太文雅了 好像歌剧结束后的喝彩
That clapping, so polite. It's like the end of the opera.
"你好 请问你的茶里要加多少糖"
"Excuse me,how many sugar u want in your tea?"
这个女人 这一年里每个周三下午都在这
This woman been spending every Wednesday afternoon for a year
跟你的丈夫 在帕丁顿的一个旅馆里
with your husband, in a hotel in Paddington.
这个男人跟你最好的朋友发生婚外情已经5年了
This guy been having an affair for five years with ur best friend.
而你的男朋友 这5年里你给了他所有的爱
Your boyfriend, what you gave ur love,ur spirit,for 5 years
而他却为了一个22岁的瑞士婊子背叛你
betrays you with a Swedish bitch, what is 22 years old.
你想杀了他 你想阉了他
You want to kill him. You want to cut off his balls.
他禽兽不如 我恨他!
He's such a bastard! I hate him!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
真没料到 还真的有故事
Didn't bargain for that. That was something else.
我知道 但她可真行
I know, but all credit to her.
她很快就恢复 直接回来了
She picked herself up. She came straight back.
就好像什么都没发生过一样 真是精力十足 对吧
As if nothing had happened Like a little fireball,wasn't she?
一点都看不出感伤      没有 擦干眼泪重来
Not a grain of sentimentality.        No,wipe the tears.
上帝保佑她 我真想抱抱她
Bless her. I wanted to give her a hug.
我觉得她不会喜欢的
I don't think she'd appreciate that.
当然不会 "不要! 这是我的世界 滚远一点"
No! "This is my space, get off me!"
不管怎么说 感觉很不好 她的心碎的散落一地
Leaves a nasty taste, exploding her heart all over floor.
然后马上又整理好      放回盒子里
Then it was "put that away".        Stick that in a box.
改天再拿出来      可能永远都不会再提
Get it out another time.        Perhaps never.
你真幸运      我知道
You'll be lucky.         I know.
她一定经历过一些很糟的事情 你觉得呢
She must be going through some shit,though,mustn't she?
她的确是个好老师      恩 是啊 的确
She's actually a good teacher.        Oh, yeah,definitely.
她想要耗尽她全部的精力
She's going to burn herself out.
她说她要阉了他的时候 我相信了 你呢?
I believed her when she said she'd cut off his balls,Didn't u?